<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-06-17T00:05:19-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Halve</title><subtitle>Stylish, Two-Column Jekyll Theme</subtitle><entry><title type="html">5 Day slump</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/5-day-slump/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="5 Day slump" /><published>2017-06-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-06-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/5-day-slump</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/5-day-slump/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;fun-and-relaxed-days&quot;&gt;Fun and Relaxed Days&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isn’t it marvelous when you have a few days strung together where you get to feel like you are yourself again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday for example was very cool, brought the girlfriend to work, slept pretty well, and decided to chill with a few people because my electricity was down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turned out to be a wonderful start to a nice week, and a really cool realization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;human-contact&quot;&gt;Human Contact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe for a lot of people this makes obvious sense, but for me this has always been a rather illusive situation. Being alone, is bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love being alone, among my thoughts, there is a relaxing &amp;amp; soothing quality to letting the ether just run through your mind. I like that visualization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But man is not designed to be alone, we thrive on the input of others, they give us new perspectives, new ways to interpret what is around ourselves. This is a good thing as well. It is the colorful contrast to the stark inner world that i create for myself. I used to fill it with brilliant and vivid science fiction or fantasy. Though now i seem to have lost the unitary focus that i once had, it is actually exhausting now to focus on one thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is much more fun to bounce from one idea to the next when you are stuck. It creates that sensation of progress and achievement, when in reality little is getting done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, it feels good to be around people, even though i am being busy trying to stay in my corner, my personality is still to abrasive most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;side-effects&quot;&gt;Side Effects&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While human contact has certainly proven beneficial to me, it still instills a certain sense of dread. Today’s world is a world where peace is more important than confrontation at all costs, skins are no longer thick and relationships are usually thinly veiled attempts at human interaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s sad that only the privileged few are permitted to act upon their behaviors. The ones who are struggling to get ahead in life can not afford to risk someone with power exacting retribution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a person that is privileged, i have been raised in a family that operates at a high social status. Etiquette and attitude are something that all must have to be accepted in my environment, as well as a certain concrete knowledge that everyone knows his place on the pyramid of success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This knowledge of how people behave on the privilege spectrum is quite traumatic most often. You are stuck consistently deciding between two methods of operating with people, and it gets worse, every new social gathering presents a fresh chance to choose how to behave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behaving with attitude when one is in a position of privilege is much like defending an oasis in a desert. People look at your oasis either with envy or with disgust. Once they have seen the oasis, the person is sublimated from his humanity, and he becomes it’s devilish guardian. Greedy and uncouth should he decide to refuse you access. With disdain or patronizing should one accidentally hurt someone’s pride by offering the precious fruits of the oasis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rarely is a person of strong enough personality and eruditeness that he sees the work and toil that has passed into a person’s little chunk of the world, or for any creation for that matter. Most often people degenerate to a more base state of mind, governed more by instinct than by reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where the crux of the problem lies, why do i as a person of reason, must suffer and dance around other’s lacking gravitas, and suffer to be trapped in their judging stare who are lesser than me in regards to their covetous stares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stalemate&quot;&gt;Stalemate&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The only winning move is to not play”, i have come to the realization, that regardless of what we do, we as humans are hardwired to judge, a survival instinct who’s adaptation to a social medium is ill equipped to handle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stalemate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;layout: “post”
 title: “test”
 date: “2017-06-16 22:21”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;lets see this.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Fun and Relaxed Days</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/redmountainsAr1.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Are Coffee Shops an IT Thing?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/CoffeeShops/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are Coffee Shops an IT Thing?" /><published>2017-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/CoffeeShops</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/CoffeeShops/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;shit-coffee-shit-internet--fucking-glare&quot;&gt;Shit Coffee, Shit Internet, &amp;amp; Fucking Glare&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Honestly, if this is the lifestyle of someone who works in the tech industry it is horrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now i think i have finally found a resource that meets my specific needs, as well as what i am going to add on top of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s from freecodecamp. And it has what i want:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Front End Dev(400h)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Visualization(400h)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Back End Dev(400h)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Project(800h)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a grand total of 2000+ hours of delicious coding.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Shit Coffee, Shit Internet, &amp;amp; Fucking Glare</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/hustle.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Night Time Design Walk</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/RandomDesignInspirations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Night Time Design Walk" /><published>2017-05-26T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/RandomDesignInspirations</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/RandomDesignInspirations/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;long-nights-spent-in-mania&quot;&gt;Long Nights Spent In Mania&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;{Wonderland-Limes}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the early hours of the morning, my back is in quite big amounts of discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few days earlier, i went to a chiropractor and had my spine &lt;em&gt;Readjusted Thoroughly&lt;/em&gt;, and now i am only comfortable on a position lying down on my back. No longer am i allowed to assume the most deliciously comfy position on earth, what i like to call the flat soldier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been very stiff for a very long time and i have had difficulty cracking my back and neck to release tension, and i seem to be compensating for the lost months, if not years, i have not stopped popping and crackling for two days straight. Though i feel as if i have two massive bruises on the inside of my cervical vertebrae, and they are sensitive to chilly situations, giving me instant pain and dizziness. What joy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beauty of today though, is that i am finding very stylish sources of inspiration, at least on a design level, from old school book cover art to all sorts of awesome artists such as &lt;em&gt;Justin Van Genderen&lt;/em&gt;, and some yummy art all over the place, for some reason consuming art is refreshing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Long Nights Spent In Mania</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/quovadis.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Random Failures</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Random-Failures/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Random Failures" /><published>2017-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Random-Failures</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Random-Failures/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;being-an-idiot-is-funny-sometimes&quot;&gt;Being an Idiot is Funny Sometimes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today i failed at a the very simple act of attending a meeting. Quite frustrated as this just demonstrates my lack of discipline and organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean how is it that in todays day and age of the tricorder, that i still forget important things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it might boil down to a few things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I do not process inputs to my schedule properly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I do not prune and maintain my calendar properly either&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I do not have it in my routine to check my calendar whatsoever.
This nice trifecta is kinda the worse system ever, there is no input to my system, no maintenance of it, &amp;amp; especially no verification of it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I must figure out a way to commit to a scheduling system.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Being an Idiot is Funny Sometimes</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/randomroad.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Doing Some Weight Lifting</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/DjangoPythonPractice/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Doing Some Weight Lifting" /><published>2017-05-20T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/DjangoPythonPractice</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/DjangoPythonPractice/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-workload-of-the-day&quot;&gt;The Workload Of The Day&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was a rather interesting exercise in upkeep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing that i have done is brush myself up on organizational issues, &amp;amp; did a small clean up of my files, while my whole computer probably needs to be nuked &amp;amp; a fresh start started, that’s a very long process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have bypassed this by setting up virtual environments &amp;amp; learning how to use them, this compartmentalizes my dependencies &amp;amp; allows me to fck up less as i chase down mistakes a lot less often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What i decided to do was to follow a django/python [tutorial] &amp;amp; pile through the tutorial, i spent the better part of 3 hours on it, &amp;amp; i have managed to have success somewhere down the line, definitely i will need to have a more in depth mastery of a few things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Github &amp;amp; command line Git&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Django commands&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But besides that i have managed nicely i think today &amp;amp; i am happy that i moved forward quite far.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Workload Of The Day</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/spiralstairs.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Return To The Bar</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/RetunToTheBar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Return To The Bar" /><published>2017-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/RetunToTheBar</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/RetunToTheBar/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;keeping-it-simple&quot;&gt;Keeping It simple&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the internet seems to be constantly reminding me, putting your face to the grinding stone is something that you have to tackle gently at first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was quite simple. Cleaned the house, taxied the girlfriend to work, skateboarded to the lakeshore &amp;amp; lost a few games of LoL.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Keeping It simple</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/grindingtheaxe.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Art Of Planning</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/theartofscheduling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Art Of Planning" /><published>2016-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/theartofscheduling</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/theartofscheduling/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-best-man-has-to-offer&quot;&gt;The Best Man Has to Offer&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Attack is the secret of defense; defense is the planning of an attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Sun Tzu&lt;cite&gt;, Art Of War&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Best Man Has to Offer</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/wrap.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Shadow Behind The Eye</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/halloween-special/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Shadow Behind The Eye" /><published>2016-10-31T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-10-31T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/halloween-special</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/halloween-special/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;part-1-----the-campfire&quot;&gt;Part 1 -   The Campfire&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We have always been afraid of the dark.
More specifically we have always been afraid of the unknown.
There is something special about our relationship with the unknown.
Through trial, error and great pain, we have managed to push away this
problematic issue. We discovered fire, and the night was forever pushed
back. We feared the elements, and we mastered them, plagues have decimated
us, and we fought back with medicine. The fear of the unknown has been our
greatest motivator to push back the darkness. I wonder, if all this time
we were allowed to grow out of the dark ages, for the amusement of those
beings that go bumping in the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Part 1 - The Campfire</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pain &amp;amp; Sweet Rewards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/first/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pain &amp; Sweet Rewards" /><published>2016-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/first</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/first/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;These are probably the most important steps in a creator’s life.
The first steps one takes in putting his energy into a creation.
This is my beginning this is my creation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Anonymous&lt;cite&gt;, Street wisdom&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-path-one-takes&quot;&gt;The Path One Takes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many &lt;em&gt;things&lt;/em&gt; have lead me to come to this Path, &amp;amp; the first thing i would like
to do right now is to present something simple, a first step so to speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe one day i will look down the line &amp;amp; find this little piece &amp;amp; look
back at myself with nostalgia, or maybe any other bag of emotions will be
leveled at my past self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As i am twiddling now a simple object in my hands, a twenty sided dice made
of smooth and entrancing black and silvery resin, it speaks to me of this creation
i am in the process of bearing forth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose a more poetic and picturesque prose for this piece, not because of design
or a desire to show off a stylistic talent, but because i feel that when one is
describing their principles and values through words, they must transmit the same
emotions from which they where built.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-first-collections&quot;&gt;The First Collections&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My whole life i have been living &amp;amp; learning in my own bubble, often times
content with absorbing the experiences that were either presented to me
or otherwise fabricated by my own version of the scientific method with a
dash of madness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes i was angry with the situation i was living in, &amp;amp; i let that fuel
bring me the energy i needed to change the situation i was in. This is usually
when i put on my mad scientist glasses on, &amp;amp; attack a problem with all the
resources that are at my disposal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The approach that i use to attack a problem usually boil down to a few concepts.
These are some of the pillars that i have built myself upon, and by no means are
these exhaustive in there presentation. Here are but a few.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;knowledge-mastery--control&quot;&gt;Knowledge, Mastery &amp;amp; Control&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Knowledge is power &amp;amp; it can command obedience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Imam-Ali&lt;cite&gt;, Saying 146&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From all that i have observed in my experiences, a person that exhibits masterful
knowledge &amp;amp; control over a subject is bestowed with qualities that any person
would envy. Namely confidence, leadership, &amp;amp; serenity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confidence&lt;/strong&gt; is at the top of this list in my opinion, regardless of wether or not
the person actually feels an absolute sense of confidence. The &lt;em&gt;gravitas&lt;/em&gt; of
a man who is aware of all the intricacies related to a subject of any worth is
quite poignant &amp;amp; oft times intimidating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leadership&lt;/strong&gt; belongs somewhere on this trifecta of qualities presented here,
but the meaning implied here is not one of directing a group of people.
Leadership here is defined as being at the top of the class, &lt;em&gt;the King of the Hill&lt;/em&gt;
so to speak. A man who exudes this quality of leadership creates &amp;amp; air about him.
Fear the the man who possesses leadership, for he is both dangerous &amp;amp; daft,
&amp;amp; the dominant &amp;amp; competitive spirit is always burning deep within him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serenity&lt;/strong&gt; is probably the most coveted quality a person could ever hope to achieve.
When a man can display a sense of absolute calm in the face of chaos, it is to
be know that regardless if he may not be a leader in his demesne, or endowed
with great confidence, it is quite a terrible site to behold. That a person can
manipulate the resources available to him in the face of strenuous odds with a
steady hand &amp;amp; ice running in his veins is a sight to behold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While i have been rather dramatic with the prose presented here. There is a
purpose. It is to paint a picture of an ideal situation, the weight of daily
life does imposes limitations on what it means to be masterful, knowledgable &amp;amp;
in control. Maybe we are fatigued, or life has dealt us an impossible hand from
which failure is night inevitable. Quite the worse of all would be those
conundrums in which regardless of the situation &amp;amp; our capacities to affect it
we are staring at failure straight into its deep &amp;amp; maddening eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Limitations &amp;amp; failures are the constant flames in which a person of humble
beginnings crafts himself into something more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!---
## Iteration, Practice &amp; Perfection
--&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">These are probably the most important steps in a creator’s life. The first steps one takes in putting his energy into a creation. This is my beginning this is my creation.</summary></entry></feed>