<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-06-17T00:08:55-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Halve</title><subtitle>Stylish, Two-Column Jekyll Theme</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Strange Missive</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/TheHourGlassman/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Strange Missive" /><published>2016-12-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-12-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/TheHourGlassman</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/TheHourGlassman/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-hourglass-mans-letter&quot;&gt;The Hourglass Man’s Letter&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darkness has befallen us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The great lineage of our family is now teetering on the precipice of oblivion. I hope that this letter has managed to reach our only remaining allies, else all our efforts shall be for naught.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have been hunting a great &lt;em&gt;Shade&lt;/em&gt; for many years now, it’s tenebrous tracks spreading death &amp;amp; devastation wherever it treads. That blasted &lt;em&gt;Shade&lt;/em&gt; finally seemed to settle in a frontier town called &lt;em&gt;The Blue Dandelion&lt;/em&gt;. The town folk at first seemed to be humble folk, their village beset by an uncommonly harsh winter &amp;amp; poor harvest, yet still their stoicism &amp;amp; eerie cheerfulness steeled our hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could not have been further from the truth, be weary my friends, nothing is what it truly seems to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few bear the &lt;em&gt;Three Cross Sigil&lt;/em&gt; of our clan of &lt;em&gt;Hunters&lt;/em&gt;. We are trapped, and this is our last effort to escape our chains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may be our final hope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grazen,
Grand Master of The Hourglass&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Hourglass Man’s Letter</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/hourglass.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Art Of Planning</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/theartofscheduling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Art Of Planning" /><published>2016-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/theartofscheduling</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/theartofscheduling/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-best-man-has-to-offer&quot;&gt;The Best Man Has to Offer&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Attack is the secret of defense; defense is the planning of an attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Sun Tzu&lt;cite&gt;, Art Of War&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Best Man Has to Offer</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/wrap.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The B.V.P Templates intro</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/theblackvelvetproject/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The B.V.P Templates intro" /><published>2016-11-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-11-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/theblackvelvetproject</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/theblackvelvetproject/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-black-velvet-project&quot;&gt;The Black Velvet Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Todo List
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Add author name to top of articles ( Alex ?)
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;clone repository&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;modify the template please&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Create Videos For all the todos ( Val )
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;% Complete ( 0% )&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;intro to video/audio production
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Good audio &amp;gt; Good video&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;How to use Davinci
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Basic editing&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Basic Color Correction&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Basic Export&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;How to use audio recording software
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Audacity&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Good Music
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Set the Mood&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Background energy&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Basics of Lighting
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Free Lighting&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;3 Point Lighting&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Basics Of Composition
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Storyboarding&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Types of shots
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Wide shots&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Sliding shots&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Close Ups&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Mid shots&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Analysis Of Composition
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;MKBHD tech review dissections&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Linus Tech Tips dissections&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;Marzbar Vlog dessctions&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Black Velvet Project</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Shadow Behind The Eye</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/halloween-special/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Shadow Behind The Eye" /><published>2016-10-31T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-10-31T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/halloween-special</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/halloween-special/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;part-1-----the-campfire&quot;&gt;Part 1 -   The Campfire&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We have always been afraid of the dark.
More specifically we have always been afraid of the unknown.
There is something special about our relationship with the unknown.
Through trial, error and great pain, we have managed to push away this
problematic issue. We discovered fire, and the night was forever pushed
back. We feared the elements, and we mastered them, plagues have decimated
us, and we fought back with medicine. The fear of the unknown has been our
greatest motivator to push back the darkness. I wonder, if all this time
we were allowed to grow out of the dark ages, for the amusement of those
beings that go bumping in the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Part 1 - The Campfire</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pain &amp;amp; Sweet Rewards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/first/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pain &amp; Sweet Rewards" /><published>2016-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2016-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/first</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/first/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;These are probably the most important steps in a creator’s life.
The first steps one takes in putting his energy into a creation.
This is my beginning this is my creation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Anonymous&lt;cite&gt;, Street wisdom&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-path-one-takes&quot;&gt;The Path One Takes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many &lt;em&gt;things&lt;/em&gt; have lead me to come to this Path, &amp;amp; the first thing i would like
to do right now is to present something simple, a first step so to speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe one day i will look down the line &amp;amp; find this little piece &amp;amp; look
back at myself with nostalgia, or maybe any other bag of emotions will be
leveled at my past self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As i am twiddling now a simple object in my hands, a twenty sided dice made
of smooth and entrancing black and silvery resin, it speaks to me of this creation
i am in the process of bearing forth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose a more poetic and picturesque prose for this piece, not because of design
or a desire to show off a stylistic talent, but because i feel that when one is
describing their principles and values through words, they must transmit the same
emotions from which they where built.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-first-collections&quot;&gt;The First Collections&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My whole life i have been living &amp;amp; learning in my own bubble, often times
content with absorbing the experiences that were either presented to me
or otherwise fabricated by my own version of the scientific method with a
dash of madness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes i was angry with the situation i was living in, &amp;amp; i let that fuel
bring me the energy i needed to change the situation i was in. This is usually
when i put on my mad scientist glasses on, &amp;amp; attack a problem with all the
resources that are at my disposal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The approach that i use to attack a problem usually boil down to a few concepts.
These are some of the pillars that i have built myself upon, and by no means are
these exhaustive in there presentation. Here are but a few.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;knowledge-mastery--control&quot;&gt;Knowledge, Mastery &amp;amp; Control&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Knowledge is power &amp;amp; it can command obedience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Imam-Ali&lt;cite&gt;, Saying 146&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From all that i have observed in my experiences, a person that exhibits masterful
knowledge &amp;amp; control over a subject is bestowed with qualities that any person
would envy. Namely confidence, leadership, &amp;amp; serenity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confidence&lt;/strong&gt; is at the top of this list in my opinion, regardless of wether or not
the person actually feels an absolute sense of confidence. The &lt;em&gt;gravitas&lt;/em&gt; of
a man who is aware of all the intricacies related to a subject of any worth is
quite poignant &amp;amp; oft times intimidating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leadership&lt;/strong&gt; belongs somewhere on this trifecta of qualities presented here,
but the meaning implied here is not one of directing a group of people.
Leadership here is defined as being at the top of the class, &lt;em&gt;the King of the Hill&lt;/em&gt;
so to speak. A man who exudes this quality of leadership creates &amp;amp; air about him.
Fear the the man who possesses leadership, for he is both dangerous &amp;amp; daft,
&amp;amp; the dominant &amp;amp; competitive spirit is always burning deep within him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serenity&lt;/strong&gt; is probably the most coveted quality a person could ever hope to achieve.
When a man can display a sense of absolute calm in the face of chaos, it is to
be know that regardless if he may not be a leader in his demesne, or endowed
with great confidence, it is quite a terrible site to behold. That a person can
manipulate the resources available to him in the face of strenuous odds with a
steady hand &amp;amp; ice running in his veins is a sight to behold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While i have been rather dramatic with the prose presented here. There is a
purpose. It is to paint a picture of an ideal situation, the weight of daily
life does imposes limitations on what it means to be masterful, knowledgable &amp;amp;
in control. Maybe we are fatigued, or life has dealt us an impossible hand from
which failure is night inevitable. Quite the worse of all would be those
conundrums in which regardless of the situation &amp;amp; our capacities to affect it
we are staring at failure straight into its deep &amp;amp; maddening eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Limitations &amp;amp; failures are the constant flames in which a person of humble
beginnings crafts himself into something more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!---
## Iteration, Practice &amp; Perfection
--&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">These are probably the most important steps in a creator’s life. The first steps one takes in putting his energy into a creation. This is my beginning this is my creation.</summary></entry></feed>